A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, William J. Ronan, Series 29 FA371
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reference Files, 1945-1971; 2; 17.4 Cubic Feet
  - Local Government - Proceedings of the Local Government Workshop, June 1960 (Box 23, Folder 271)
  - Local Government - Proceedings of the Local Government Workshop, June 1961 (Box 23, Folder 272)
  - Local Government - 1961-1962 Annual Report, Office for Local Government, John J. Burns, Chairman (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Motor Vehicles - 1958 Annual Report, Department of Taxation and Finance, Bureau of Motor Vehicles, William S. Hults, Commissioner (Box 24, Folder 274)
  - Motor Vehicles - 1959 Annual Report, Department of Taxation and Finance, Bureau of Motor Vehicles, William S. Hults, Commissioner (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - Motor Vehicles - 1960 Annual Report, Department of Taxation and Finance, Bureau of Motor Vehicles, William S. Hults, Commissioner (Box 24, Folder 276)
  - Motor Vehicles - Achievements in Motor Vehicle Administration in New York State, 1959-1962 (Box 24, Folder 277)
  - Motor Vehicles - Pedestrian Accidents in New York State, 1943-1962 (Box 24, Folder 278)
  - Motor Vehicles - 1963 Annual Report, Department of Taxation and Finance, Bureau of Motor Vehicles, William S. Hults, Commissioner (Box 24, Folder 279)
  - Motor Vehicles - Planning Bureau Report for 1963 (Box 24, Folder 280)
  - Motor Vehicles - 1963 Accident Facts, New York State Department of Motor Vehicles (Box 24, Folder 281)
  - Thruway Authority - Financial Reports, December 1958 (Box 24, Folder 282)
  - Thruway Authority - Financial Report, March 1959 (Box 24, Folder 283)
  - Thruway Authority - Thruway Operations Report, March 1959 (Box 24, Folder 284)
  - Thruway Authority - Twelfth Annual Report, 1961, New York State Thruway Authority, R. Burdell Bixby, Chairman (Box 24, Folder 285)
  - Thruway Authority - Thruway Operations Report, Third Quarter 1962 (Box 24, Folder 286)
  - Power - State of New York, Governor's Committee on Power Resources, December 1959 (Box 24, Folder 287)
  - Power - Niagara - St. Lawrence Power Projects, Construction Progress, April-November 1959, Power Authority of the State of New York, Robert Moses, Chairman (Box 24, Folder 288)
  - Power - Niagara - St. Lawrence Power Projects, Construction Progress, April-December 1960, Power Authority of the State of New York, Robert Moses, Chairman (Box 24, Folder 289)
  - Power - Niagara - St. Lawrence Power Projects, Construction Progress, January-September 1961, Power Authority of the State of New York, Robert Moses, Chairman (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Power - Niagara - St. Lawrence Power Projects, Construction Progress, First Quarter 1962, Power Authority of the State of New York, Robert Moses, Chairman (Box 24, Folder 291)
  - Civil Defense - 1958 Annual Report, J. Burch McMorran, Acting Chairman, New York State Civil Defense Commission (Box 25, Folder 292)
  - Civil Defense - 1959 Annual Report, General Anthony C. McAuliffe, Chairman, New York State Civil Defense Commission (Box 25, Folder 293)
  - Civil Defense - 1960 Annual Report, General Anthony C. McAuliffe, Chairman, New York State Civil Defense Commission (Box 25, Folder 294)
  - Civil Defense - 1961 Annual Report, General Anthony C. McAuliffe, Chairman, New York State Civil Defense Commission (Box 25, Folder 295)
  - Civil Defense - 1962 Annual Report, General Anthony C. McAuliffe, Chairman, New York State Civil Defense Commission (Box 25, Folder 296)
  - Labor Relations Board - Twenty-third Annual Analysis of Decisions, 1959, New York State Labor Relations Board, Jay Kramer, Chairman (Box 25, Folder 297)
  - Labor Relations Board - Twenty-fourth Annual Analysis of Decisions, 1960, New York State Labor Relations Board, Jay Kramer, Chairman (Box 25, Folder 298)
  - Labor Relations Board - Twenty-fifth Annual Analysis of Decisions, 1961, New York State Labor Relations Board, Jay Kramer, Chairman (Box 25, Folder 299)
  - Labor Relations Board - Twenty-sixth Annual Analysis of Decisions, 1962, New York State Labor Relations Board, Jay Kramer, Chairman (Box 25, Folder 300)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, June 1960, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 301)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, July 1960, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 302)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, September 1960, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Organizational Charts, Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, September 1960 (Box 25, Folder 303)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, November 1960, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Survey Report on the Rental and Housing Market, January 1961 (Box 25, Folder 306)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, January 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 307)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, February-March 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 308)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, May 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 309)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, June 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 310)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, July-August 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 311)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, September 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 312)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - Report of the Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, December 1961, Robert E. Herman, Commissioner and State Rent Administrator (Box 25, Folder 313)
  - Temporary State Housing Rent Commission - 1962 Report of Operations, State Housing Rent Commission (Box 25, Folder 314)
  - Port Authority of New York - 1961 Annual Report, S. Sloat Colt, Chairman (Box 26, Folder 315)
  - Port Authority of New York - 1962 Annual Report, S. Sloat Colt, Chairman (Box 26, Folder 316)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - Report of the Surgeon General's Consultant Group on Medical Education, "Physicians for a Growing America," October 1959 (Box 26, Folder 317)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - Health, Education, and Welfare Trends, 1960 Edition (Box 26, Folder 318)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - "The National and Its Older People," Report of the White House Conference on Aging, January 9-12, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 319)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - "Aging with a Future," Reports and Guidelines from the White House Conference on Aging, April 1961 (Box 26, Folder 320)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - "Employment Security and Retirement of the Older Worker," Reports and Guidelines from the White House Conference on Aging, April 1961 (Box 26, Folder 321)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - "Impact of Inflation on Retired Persons," Reports and Guidelines from the White House Conference on Aging, April 1961 (Box 26, Folder 322)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - "Income Maintenance, Including Financing of Health Costs," Reports and Guidelines from the White House Conference on Aging, April 1961 (Box 26, Folder 323)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - Health, Education, and Welfare Trends, 1962 Edition (Box 26, Folder 324)
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - "Work Relief ... A Current Look," March 1962 (Box 26, Folder 325)
  - National Security - "Organizing for National Security, The Executive Office and Public Support," Hearings Before the Subcommittee on National Policy Machinery of the Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, July 1960 (Box 26, Folder 326)
  - National Security - "Organizing for National Security, Super-Cabinet Officers and Superstaffs," Study Submitted to the Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, by its Subcommittee on National Policy Machinery, November 1960 (Box 26, Folder 327)
  - National Security - "Organizing for National Security," Inquiry of the Subcommittee on National Policy Machinery, Senator Henry M. Jackson, Chairman, Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, Volume 1 - Hearings, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 328)
  - National Security - "Organizing for National Security," Inquiry of the Subcommittee on National Policy Machinery, Senator Henry M. Jackson, Chairman, Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, Volume 2 - Studies and Background Materials, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 329)
  - National Security - "Organizing for National Security," Inquiry of the Subcommittee on National Policy Machinery, Senator Henry M. Jackson, Chairman, Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, Volume 3 - Staff Reports and Recommendations, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 330)
  - National Security - "Organizing for National Security, State, Defense, and the National Security Council," Hearings Before the Subcommittee on National Policy Machinery of the Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, August 1961 (Box 27, Folder 331)
  - National Security - "Administration of National Security," Hearings Before the Subcommittee on National Security Staffing and Operations of the Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, March 1963 (Box 27, Folder 332)
  - National Security - "Administration of National Security," Hearings Before the Subcommittee on National Security Staffing and Operations of the Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, June 1964 (Box 27, Folder 333)
  - Government Operations - "Problems of Federal State-Local Relations"; "Government in Metropolitan Areas," Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations of the Committee on Government Relations, United States Senate, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 334)
  - Government Operations - "Disposal of Ellis Island (New York Harbor)," Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations of the Committee on Government Operations, United States Senate, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 335)
  - Small Business - Hearings before the Select Committee on Small Business, House of Representatives, March, August, November 1955 (Box 28, Folder 336)
  - Small Business - "Distribution Problems," Hearings Before the Select Committee on Small Business, House of Representatives, March-June 1955 (Box 28, Folder 337)
  - Small Business - "The Small Business Administration and Related Activities," Hearings Before the Select Committee on Small Business, House of Representatives, March 1955 (Box 28, Folder 338)
  - Small Business - Sixth Annual Report of the Select Committee on Small Business, United States Senate, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 339)
  - Child Welfare - Report to the President, "A Proposed Program for National Action to Combat Mental Retardation," The President's Panel on Mental Retardation, October 1962 (Box 28, Folder 340)
  - Child Welfare - Recommendations - Composite Report of Forum Findings, 1960 White House Conference on Children and Youth, April 1960 (Box 28, Folder 341)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service - Thirteenth Annual Report, Fiscal Year 1960, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, Joseph F. Finnegan, Director (Box 29, Folder 342)
  - Nuclear Attack Recovery/Civil Defense - Digest of Soviet Civil Defence, May 1962; Digest of Civil Defense in Sweden, May 1962; Digest of West German Economic Recovery Through Social Free Economy, May 1962 (Box 29, Folder 343)
  - Nuclear Attack Recovery/Civil Defense - Preliminary Statement, June 1962, New York State Committee on Nuclear Attack (Box 29, Folder 344)
  - Nuclear Attack Recovery/Civil Defense - "Shelter Designs for Protection Against Radioactive Fallout," Report to the Institute of Public Administration, February 1960 (Box 29, Folder 345)
  - Conservation/Preservation - "The Protection and Preservation of the Atlantic Shore Front of the State of New York," Report of the Temporary State Commission on Protection and Preservation of the Atlantic Shore Front, Joseph F. Carlino, Chairman, June 1962 (Box 29, Folder 346)
  - Agriculture - "Full Prosperity for Agriculture," Conference on Economic Progress, Washington, D.C., November 1955 (Box 29, Folder 347)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Report of the Temporary State Commission on Coordination of State Activities, February 1959 (Box 29, Folder 348)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Report of the Temporary State Commission on Coordination of State Activities, February 1959, part 2 (Box 30, Folder 349)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Buffalo, December 1960 (Box 30, Folder 350)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Buffalo, December 1960 (Box 30, Folder 351)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Syracuse, October 1960 (Box 30, Folder 352)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Syracuse, October 1960 (Box 30, Folder 353)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Syracuse, copy 2, October 1960 (Box 30, Folder 354)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Syracuse, copy 2, October 1960 (Box 30, Folder 355)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Buffalo, Volume 3, December 1960 (Box 31, Folder 356)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Buffalo, copy 2, December 1960 (Box 31, Folder 357)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, Buffalo, copy 2, December 1960 (Box 31, Folder 358)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, New York City, November 1960 (Box 31, Folder 359)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, New York City, November 1960 (Box 31, Folder 360)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, New York City, November 1960 (Box 31, Folder 361)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Minutes of Public Hearing, Subcommittee on Public Welfare, New York City, November 1960 (Box 31, Folder 362)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Report of the Temporary State Commission on Coordination of State Activities, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 363)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Responsibility in Urban Regional Development," the Council of State Governments, July 1962 (Box 32, Folder 364)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "A Guide for Highway Safety," Prepared by the Committee on Roads and Highway Safety of the Governor's Conference, the Council of State Governments, July 1963 (Box 32, Folder 365)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Juvenile Delinquency," A Report on State Action and Responsibilities, the Council of State Governments, July 1962 (Box 32, Folder 366)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Planning," A Policy Statement, the Council of State Governments, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 367)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Report of the Joint Federal-State Action Committee to the President of the United States and to the Chairman of the Governor's Conference, Progress Report #1, December 1957 (Box 32, Folder 368)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Second Report of the Joint Federal-State Action Committee to the President of the United States and to the Chairman of the Governor's Conference, Progress Report #2, December 1958 (Box 32, Folder 369)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Autumn 1958, Published by the Council of State Governments, One issue (Box 32, Folder 370)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Spring 1959, Autumn 1959, Winter 1959, Published by the Council of State Governments, Three issues (Box 32, Folder 371)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Summer 1960, Published by the Council of State Governments, One issue (Box 32, Folder 372)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Summer 1961, Autumn 1961, Published by the Council of State Governments, Two issues (Box 32, Folder 373)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Spring 1962, Autumn 1962, Winter 1962, Published by the Council of State Governments, Three issues (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Spring 1963, Summer 1963, Winter 1963, Published by the Council of State Governments, Three issues (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Government," "The Journal of State Affairs," Spring 1964, Summer 1964, Winter 1964, Published by the Council of State Governments, Three issues (Box 33, Folder 376)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Suggested State Regulations for Control of Radiation," Prepared by the Council of State Governments in Cooperation with the U.S. Atomic Energy Commission and the U.S. Public Health Service, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 377)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Current Salaries in State Mental Health Programs," Interstate Clearing House on Mental Health, Council of State Governments, November 1958 (Box 33, Folder 378)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Interstate Relationships in the Taxation of Commercial Vehicles," A Preliminary Report Prepared for the Board of Managers of the Council of State Governments, January 1959 (Box 33, Folder 379)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Constitutional and Statutory Provisions of the States," January 1959 (Box 33, Folder 380)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Organization and Finance in the Field of Mental Health Research," A State by State Survey, October 1959 (Box 33, Folder 381)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Courts and the Commonplaces of Federalism," by Walter V. Schaefer, Justice of the Supreme Court of Illinois, Reproduced with the Permission of the Institute of Government and Public Affairs, University of Illinois, by the Council of State Governments, February 1959 (Box 33, Folder 382)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Suggested State Legislation," Program for 1959, Developed by the Committee of State Officials on Suggested State Legislation of the Council of State Governments, October 1958 (Box 33, Folder 383)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Patterns of Intergovernmental Cooperation," January 1959 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Suggested State Legislation," Program for 1960, Developed by the Committee of State Officials on Suggested State Legislation of the Council of State Governments, October 1959 (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Reciprocal State Legislation to Enforce the Support of Dependents," 1960 Edition (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Proceedings of the National Governor's Conference on Delinquency and Youth Crime, October 1961 (Box 34, Folder 387)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Action in the Field of Aging," 1960-1961, A Progress Report, April 1962 (Box 34, Folder 388)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Radiation Control Act," Reprinted from the "Suggested State Legislation," Program for 1960 (Box 34, Folder 389)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Technical Assistance to Local Governments," 1962 (Box 34, Folder 390)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "The Driver License Compact and the Vehicle Equipment Safety Compact," January 1962 (Box 34, Folder 391)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "To Improve Cooperation Among the States," Report on the Committee on Strengthening Interstate Cooperation Commissions, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 392)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Program of Suggested State Legislation, 1962," Developed by the Committee of State Officials on Suggested State Legislation of the Council of State Governments, November 1961 (Box 34, Folder 393)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Capitol Budgeting," July 1963 (Box 34, Folder 394)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Laws Dealing with Non-Discrimination in Employment," July 1963 (Box 34, Folder 395)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Index to Council of State Governments Publications, 1960-1963 (Box 34, Folder 396)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Program of Suggested State Legislation, 1963," Developed by the Committee of State Officials on Suggested State Legislation of the Council of State Governments, October 1962 (Box 34, Folder 397)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Actions in the States in the Fields of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Related Areas," Interstate Clearing House on Mental Health, the Council of State Governments, April 1963 (Box 35, Folder 398)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Members of State Courts of Last Resort and Their Terms of Office," A Compilation Prepared for the Conference of Chief Justices, April 1963 (Box 35, Folder 399)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Units on Aging," July 1964 (Box 35, Folder 400)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Program of Suggested State Legislation, 1964," Developed by the Committee of State Officials on Suggested State Legislation of the Council of State Governments, October 1963 (Box 35, Folder 401)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Surface Mining - Extent and Economic Importance, Impact on Natural Resources, and Proposals for Reclamation of Mined-lands," Proceedings of a Conference on Surface Mining Called by the Council of State Governments, Roanoke, Virginia, June 1964 (Box 35, Folder 402)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Legislators and Selected Officials in Louisiana," April 1964 (Box 35, Folder 403)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "A Statistical Summary Prepared for the Conference of Chief Justices," July 1964 (Box 35, Folder 404)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "State Units on Aging," April 1964 (Box 35, Folder 405)